<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
<Products>
<Product>
<Supplier><![CDATA[OUTMK]]></Supplier>
<Supplier_Name><![CDATA[Trail Card]]></Supplier_Name>
<Family><![CDATA[Accessories]]></Family>
<Part_Number><![CDATA[PN30715]]></Part_Number>
<Master_Part><![CDATA[]]></Master_Part>
<Weight><![CDATA[.2000]]></Weight>
<Tax_Code><![CDATA[T1]]></Tax_Code>
<Part_type><![CDATA[1]]></Part_type>
<Supplier_Part><![CDATA[GC400]]></Supplier_Part>
<Description><![CDATA[Snowshoeing Mont Blanc/Western Alps]]></Description>
<Full_Description><![CDATA[For centuries people have used snowshoes as a means of travelling in deep snow, but only relatively recently has snowshoeing become an activity that people do for pleasure. Nowadays, visit any winter ski resort and you'll not only find crowds of people heading for the ski runs but also a considerable number setting out on snowshoes.This book aims to show the keen hill-walker what snowshoeing can offer if you can walk you can snowshoe! Equipped correctly, with reasonable knowledge of winter conditions and dangers, you can enjoy hiking in the winter in terrain that would otherwise be inaccessible on foot. The Mont Blanc region of the European Alps is the perfect destination for a snowshoeing holiday, be it at a beginner level or for those with more experience who seek the heady joys of summits and treks in winter. This guide not only selects some of the best walks, hikes and treks in the region, all more or less within sight of Mont Blanc (given a clear day, good eyesight and some imagination), but it will also prepare you for the experience. There are sections on equipment, technique, hazards, preparation and nature, as well as 70 outings, ranging from the very gentle to the particularly strenuous. Each walk description is accompanied by practical information, timings and grade, and the routes are illustrated on clear overview maps.]]></Full_Description>
<Colour><![CDATA[]]></Colour>
<Size><![CDATA[]]></Size>
<Trade_Price><![CDATA[8.960000]]></Trade_Price>
<SRP><![CDATA[14.000000]]></SRP>
<Our_Price><![CDATA[]]></Our_Price>
<BMC><![CDATA[12.600000]]></BMC>
<Contract><![CDATA[12.600000]]></Contract>
<Clearance><![CDATA[]]></Clearance>
<Free_Stock><![CDATA[1.0000]]></Free_Stock>
</Product>
<Product>
<Supplier><![CDATA[OUTMK]]></Supplier>
<Supplier_Name><![CDATA[Trail Card]]></Supplier_Name>
<Family><![CDATA[UK Maps]]></Family>
<Part_Number><![CDATA[PN30717]]></Part_Number>
<Master_Part><![CDATA[]]></Master_Part>
<Weight><![CDATA[.2000]]></Weight>
<Tax_Code><![CDATA[T1]]></Tax_Code>
<Part_type><![CDATA[1]]></Part_type>
<Supplier_Part><![CDATA[GC384]]></Supplier_Part>
<Description><![CDATA[* Via Ferratas Italy Dolomites Vol 1]]></Description>
<Full_Description><![CDATA[The first of a two-volume set of guides to Via Ferratas of the Italian Dolomites. This guide covers the North, Central and Eastern Dolomites, across an area stretching from Val di Fassa to Auronzo, while Volume 2 covers the Southern Dolomites, Brenta and Lake Garda. Volume 1 includes areas such as Catinaccio, Marmolada, Sella, Puez Odle, Fanes, Tofane, Cristallo, Sesto, Sorapiss, Marmarole. The guide sets the routes out according to strategic valley bases, with some guidance on the best bases for attacking each of the routes. The authors have had first-hand knowledge of all the routes, and have developed a completely new grading system, which strives to simplify an extremely subjective topic.]]></Full_Description>
<Colour><![CDATA[]]></Colour>
<Size><![CDATA[]]></Size>
<Trade_Price><![CDATA[9.570000]]></Trade_Price>
<SRP><![CDATA[14.950000]]></SRP>
<Our_Price><![CDATA[]]></Our_Price>
<BMC><![CDATA[13.460000]]></BMC>
<Contract><![CDATA[13.460000]]></Contract>
<Clearance><![CDATA[]]></Clearance>
<Free_Stock><![CDATA[10.0000]]></Free_Stock>
</Product>
<Product>
<Supplier><![CDATA[OUTMK]]></Supplier>
<Supplier_Name><![CDATA[Trail Card]]></Supplier_Name>
<Family><![CDATA[UK Maps]]></Family>
<Part_Number><![CDATA[PN30721]]></Part_Number>
<Master_Part><![CDATA[]]></Master_Part>
<Weight><![CDATA[.2000]]></Weight>
<Tax_Code><![CDATA[T1]]></Tax_Code>
<Part_type><![CDATA[1]]></Part_type>
<Supplier_Part><![CDATA[C406]]></Supplier_Part>
<Description><![CDATA[Via Ferrata Italy Dolomites Vol 2]]></Description>
<Full_Description><![CDATA[This is the second in a series of two guidebooks to Via Ferratas of the Italian Dolomites. (Volume One covers the eastern, northern and central areas of the Dolomites, while Volume Two completes the picture, focusing on the southern, Brenta and Lake Garda areas.) Book Two documents Via Ferrata routes in the major mountain ranges of Civetta, Schiara and Pala as well as those to the west in the Brenta. A significant addition (and, as far as we are aware, not previously published in any English language guidebook) is the inclusion of routes around the northern end of Lake Garda and the Piccole Dolomites north of Vicenza. Here the mountains are generally lower and you can enjoy ferrata climbing over a much extended season, with some routes accessible for most of the year.]]></Full_Description>
<Colour><![CDATA[]]></Colour>
<Size><![CDATA[]]></Size>
<Trade_Price><![CDATA[10.210000]]></Trade_Price>
<SRP><![CDATA[15.950000]]></SRP>
<Our_Price><![CDATA[]]></Our_Price>
<BMC><![CDATA[14.360000]]></BMC>
<Contract><![CDATA[14.360000]]></Contract>
<Clearance><![CDATA[]]></Clearance>
<Free_Stock><![CDATA[5.0000]]></Free_Stock>
</Product>
<Product>
<Supplier><![CDATA[OUTMK]]></Supplier>
<Supplier_Name><![CDATA[Trail Card]]></Supplier_Name>
<Family><![CDATA[UK Maps]]></Family>
<Part_Number><![CDATA[PN30724]]></Part_Number>
<Master_Part><![CDATA[]]></Master_Part>
<Weight><![CDATA[.2000]]></Weight>
<Tax_Code><![CDATA[T2]]></Tax_Code>
<Part_type><![CDATA[1]]></Part_type>
<Supplier_Part><![CDATA[GC428]]></Supplier_Part>
<Description><![CDATA[Kilimanjaro Complete Trekkers Guide]]></Description>
<Full_Description><![CDATA["Kilimanjaro, a national park and a World Heritage Site, is Africa's highest mountain, the world's tallest freestanding massif and one of the world's largest volcanoes. This snow­capped dormant volcano towers almost 5km above Tanzania's savannah. Yet it is"]]></Full_Description>
<Colour><![CDATA[]]></Colour>
<Size><![CDATA[]]></Size>
<Trade_Price><![CDATA[9.570000]]></Trade_Price>
<SRP><![CDATA[14.950000]]></SRP>
<Our_Price><![CDATA[]]></Our_Price>
<BMC><![CDATA[13.460000]]></BMC>
<Contract><![CDATA[13.460000]]></Contract>
<Clearance><![CDATA[]]></Clearance>
<Free_Stock><![CDATA[5.0000]]></Free_Stock>
</Product>
<Product>
<Supplier><![CDATA[OUTMK]]></Supplier>
<Supplier_Name><![CDATA[Trail Card]]></Supplier_Name>
<Family><![CDATA[UK Maps]]></Family>
<Part_Number><![CDATA[PN30733]]></Part_Number>
<Master_Part><![CDATA[]]></Master_Part>
<Weight><![CDATA[.2000]]></Weight>
<Tax_Code><![CDATA[T1]]></Tax_Code>
<Part_type><![CDATA[1]]></Part_type>
<Supplier_Part><![CDATA[GC445]]></Supplier_Part>
<Description><![CDATA[Scrambles Lakes Vol 1 South]]></Description>
<Full_Description><![CDATA[It sometimes seems that there are no inviolate places remaining to the adventurer in the Lake District. But this is not quite the case. Scrambling - ascending rock that is not usually difficult or steep enough to warrent the term 'rock climbing' - can take you to many exiting places, many well removed from the beaten track.Even in popular areas of the Lake District, by combining several scrambles you can often hardly touch a path and rarely see other people at close quarters. A good long scramble with interesting route finding gives a very satisfying way of exploring England's Lake District.]]></Full_Description>
<Colour><![CDATA[]]></Colour>
<Size><![CDATA[]]></Size>
<Trade_Price><![CDATA[8.960000]]></Trade_Price>
<SRP><![CDATA[14.000000]]></SRP>
<Our_Price><![CDATA[]]></Our_Price>
<BMC><![CDATA[12.600000]]></BMC>
<Contract><![CDATA[12.600000]]></Contract>
<Clearance><![CDATA[]]></Clearance>
<Free_Stock><![CDATA[2.0000]]></Free_Stock>
</Product>
<Product>
<Supplier><![CDATA[OUTMK]]></Supplier>
<Supplier_Name><![CDATA[Trail Card]]></Supplier_Name>
<Family><![CDATA[UK Maps]]></Family>
<Part_Number><![CDATA[PN30734]]></Part_Number>
<Master_Part><![CDATA[]]></Master_Part>
<Weight><![CDATA[.2000]]></Weight>
<Tax_Code><![CDATA[T1]]></Tax_Code>
<Part_type><![CDATA[1]]></Part_type>
<Supplier_Part><![CDATA[GC457]]></Supplier_Part>
<Description><![CDATA[Scrambles Lakes Vol 2 North]]></Description>
<Full_Description><![CDATA[The second of a two-volume set of guides to scrambles in the Lake District.The set are based on 'Scrambles in the Lake District' and 'More Scrambles in the Lake District', two of the original scrambling guides to the Lake District by one of Britain's best-known climbers. Continually reprinted for 20 years these guides have now been fully updated and merged into two definitive guides, for southern and northern Lakes. (For details of 'Scrambles in the Lake District South', see below.) The Lake District's rich mix of rocks, gills and crags offers the scrambler a complex variety of routes, often well removed from the beaten track. Scrambling - ascending rock that is not usually difficult or steep enough to warrant the term 'rock climbing' - means you often hardly touch a path and rarely see other people at close quarters. This is a way of getting back to a wilder Lakeland and enjoying the freedom of rough mountain country.]]></Full_Description>
<Colour><![CDATA[]]></Colour>
<Size><![CDATA[]]></Size>
<Trade_Price><![CDATA[8.960000]]></Trade_Price>
<SRP><![CDATA[14.000000]]></SRP>
<Our_Price><![CDATA[]]></Our_Price>
<BMC><![CDATA[12.600000]]></BMC>
<Contract><![CDATA[12.600000]]></Contract>
<Clearance><![CDATA[]]></Clearance>
<Free_Stock><![CDATA[1.0000]]></Free_Stock>
</Product>
<Product>
<Supplier><![CDATA[OUTMK]]></Supplier>
<Supplier_Name><![CDATA[Trail Card]]></Supplier_Name>
<Family><![CDATA[UK Maps]]></Family>
<Part_Number><![CDATA[PN30748]]></Part_Number>
<Master_Part><![CDATA[]]></Master_Part>
<Weight><![CDATA[.2000]]></Weight>
<Tax_Code><![CDATA[T1]]></Tax_Code>
<Part_type><![CDATA[1]]></Part_type>
<Supplier_Part><![CDATA[GC463]]></Supplier_Part>
<Description><![CDATA[Snow Mini Guide]]></Description>
<Full_Description><![CDATA[This practical guide is aimed at walkers, climbers and snowsport enthusiasts who want to acquire or improve their knowledge of snow and avalanche release. It is equally suitable for snow professionals, guides, mountaineering and snowsport instructors, and ski patrollers.Translated by Blyth Wright, it describes the formation and evolution of snow, and shows practical methods for examining and analysing snow cover. It illustrates how to identify the many forms which snow may take and how to assess avalanche risk more precisely and reliably.It includes a system of snow observation and a handy snow crystal card for identifying crystals in the snow layer.]]></Full_Description>
<Colour><![CDATA[]]></Colour>
<Size><![CDATA[]]></Size>
<Trade_Price><![CDATA[5.110000]]></Trade_Price>
<SRP><![CDATA[8.990000]]></SRP>
<Our_Price><![CDATA[]]></Our_Price>
<BMC><![CDATA[8.090000]]></BMC>
<Contract><![CDATA[8.090000]]></Contract>
<Clearance><![CDATA[]]></Clearance>
<Free_Stock><![CDATA[10.0000]]></Free_Stock>
</Product>
</Products>
</root>
