<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
<Items>
<Item>
<ID>1</ID>
<CODE><![CDATA[PN11040]]></CODE>
<CATCODE>8006, 15004, 15013</CATCODE>
<SDESC><![CDATA[Product Dimensions: 25.4 x 68.6 x 35.6 cm ; 1.5 Kg]]></SDESC>
<DESC><![CDATA[This Futura Pro backpack features a revised carrying system for comfortable lengthy day hikes and multi-day mountain excursions. Its Aircomfort back ventilation system allows you to hold out longer and its precision features match perfectly. Deuter use Aircomfort and an air mesh to ensure moisture can escape in three directions. The ventilation pads are soft and have been designed ergonomically to provide extra comfort. The Aircomfort system reduces perspiration, thereby reducing the strain on circulation and ensuring greater stamina. This is the Pro version of that system.Aircomfort Pro combines ventilation, flexible carry comfort and a comfortable, snug hip belt. The key to this clever combination lies in its frame construction and the floating Vari Flex hip belt.Features:*Compact, anatomically formed Vari Flex hip belt in bi-laminate construction and with Wide Air-Mesh cover*Pull-Forward closure allows the hip belt to be easily tightened*Side compression straps on the hip belt*Anatomically cut Wide Air-Mesh shoulder straps with load adjusters*Side bellows pockets*Lid pocket*Zipped front pocket*Stretch outer pockets*Inner valuables pocket*Wet laundry pocket*Loops for ice axe and walking poles*Gear loops on the lid*Reflective attachment for drinking tubeSpecification:*Weight: 1640g*Volume: 38l and 5l side pockets*Measurements: 70 x 35 x 26 cm (H x W x D)]]></DESC>
<NAME><![CDATA[Futura Pro 38 ]]></NAME>
<SRP>105.00</SRP>
<OUR_PRICE>94.50</OUR_PRICE>
<CLEAR>0.00</CLEAR>
<BMC>85.05</BMC>
<CONTRACT>82.69</CONTRACT>
<WEIGHT>38.0000</WEIGHT>
<QTY>10</QTY>
</Item>
<Item>
<ID>2</ID>
<CODE><![CDATA[PN4506]]></CODE>
<CATCODE>5005, 7000, 16005</CATCODE>
<SDESC><![CDATA[Item Weight: 1.1 Kg]]></SDESC>
<DESC><![CDATA[Series 25 includes somewhat larger stoves suitable for groups of about 3-4 people. They are excellent family stoves with large pans, a wider frypan and a bigger kettle. With the supports in the raised position, the stove can be used with large billies from the rest of the Trangia range. All the stove systems in the 25 series have two saucepans (1.75 and 1.5 litres), a 22 cm frying pan, windshields (upper and lower), a burner, a pan grip and a strap. Dimensions 22 x 10.5 cm. ]]></DESC>
<NAME><![CDATA[Trangia 25/5 Non Stick + Gas Burner  ]]></NAME>
<SRP>115.00</SRP>
<OUR_PRICE>0.00</OUR_PRICE>
<CLEAR>74.97</CLEAR>
<BMC>74.97</BMC>
<CONTRACT>74.97</CONTRACT>
<WEIGHT>42.0000</WEIGHT>
<QTY>25</QTY>
</Item>
<Item>
<ID>3</ID>
<CODE><![CDATA[PN8825]]></CODE>
<CATCODE>120031, 15008, 120097</CATCODE>
<SDESC><![CDATA[Thickness : Heayy-weight
Outer Fabric / Membrane : Polartec
Recommended Use : Hiking &amp; Trekking, Traditional Climbing, Ice-fall Climbing, Alpine Skiing

]]></SDESC>
<DESC><![CDATA[The North Face Womens 200 Shadow Full Zip is a soft, midweight fleece that keeps outdoor athletes warm on long, cold autumn hikes. Extremely versatile, the Shadow can be worn on its own or under another layer for greater protection in freezing conditions. Features Fabric: Polartec Classic 200 Bluesign approvedFull-length centre front zip2 zippered hand pockets Glossary Polartec Classic 200:Available in a variety of unique textures and weights designed to enhance performance in a variety of environs. Polartec Classic 100, 200 and 300 fleeces are respectively, lightweight, midweight, and heavyweight and provide warmth, comfort and breathability. All fabrics in this series feature a patented, bi-component knit construction that uses different yarns on either side of the fabric. This creates two difference surfaces: one that is optimised to move moisture away from the skin, the other to dry quickly. Bluesign:Companies who gear their production to the bluesign Standard guarantee their direct customers and the consumer that, throughout the entire manufacturing chain, only those components and processes are used which are safe for humans and the environment.]]></DESC>
<NAME><![CDATA[Womens 200 Shadow Full Zip]]></NAME>
<SRP>70.00</SRP>
<OUR_PRICE>0.00</OUR_PRICE>
<CLEAR>41.97</CLEAR>
<BMC>41.97</BMC>
<CONTRACT>41.97</CONTRACT>
<WEIGHT>12.7500</WEIGHT>
<QTY>2</QTY>
</Item>
<Item>
<ID>4</ID>
<CODE><![CDATA[PN8866]]></CODE>
<CATCODE>8006, 8011, 120073</CATCODE>
<SDESC><![CDATA[If you're looking for a pack that will hold all your kit and more, then the Berghaus Freeflow II 40 Rucksack will be just what you are looking for]]></SDESC>
<DESC><![CDATA[
If you're looking for a pack that will hold all your kit and more, then the Berghaus Freeflow II 40 Rucksack will be just what you are looking for. It stores a rather healthy 40L of capacity perfect for Duke of Edinburgh expeditions, hiking, trekking or overnight stays. It has an abundance of zipped pockets that will keep your personal things secure and two side mesh pockets for bottles or anything you want to grab easily. It boasts the Freeflow V back-system that allows air to flow by keeping the pack away from your back. The shoulder harness has a sliding mechanism that fits the pack to you, giving you the ultimate in comfort and flexibility. If you want to put your poles aside and become hands free then no problem, there are pole straps on the front of the pack. They really have thought of everything with this pack, and it will give you peace of mind and leave you to enjoy the trek!]]></DESC>
<NAME><![CDATA[Freeflow 40]]></NAME>
<SRP>90.00</SRP>
<OUR_PRICE>72.00</OUR_PRICE>
<CLEAR>0.00</CLEAR>
<BMC>64.80</BMC>
<CONTRACT>63.00</CONTRACT>
<WEIGHT>52.0000</WEIGHT>
<QTY>7</QTY>
</Item>
<Item>
<ID>5</ID>
<CODE><![CDATA[PN8868]]></CODE>
<CATCODE>8006, 15001, 12009</CATCODE>
<SDESC><![CDATA[The Berghaus Freeflow II 30 Rucksack is a great pack for trekking, hikes or Duke of Edinburgh and will hold 30L, so you can be sure to get everything in]]></SDESC>
<DESC><![CDATA[
The Berghaus Freeflow II 30 Rucksack is a great pack for trekking, hikes or Duke of Edinburgh and will hold 30L, so you can be sure to get everything in. It has lots of handy storage areas for easy and quick access and benefits from side compression straps so the pack can be expanded when required. The shoulder straps are vented and also benefit from an adjustable harness system so the pack can fit to your specific back length. The back panel has a Freeflow V back-system which holds the back of the pack slightly away from you giving total air flow keeping you cool when you need it. It also comes with a very handy rain cover for unpredictable weather. There are straps to hold onto your walking poles, allowing you to become hands free and a waist harness making sure you're secure. A great all-rounder that will perform and leave you free to enjoy your hike!]]></DESC>
<NAME><![CDATA[Freeflow 30]]></NAME>
<SRP>80.00</SRP>
<OUR_PRICE>64.00</OUR_PRICE>
<CLEAR>0.00</CLEAR>
<BMC>57.60</BMC>
<CONTRACT>56.00</CONTRACT>
<WEIGHT>52.0000</WEIGHT>
<QTY>4</QTY>
</Item>
<Item>
<ID>6</ID>
<CODE><![CDATA[PN9021]]></CODE>
<CATCODE>2005, 110022, 6001</CATCODE>
<SDESC><![CDATA[Materials : TPU
Translucent TPU
Quickly adjustable
Weight : 13 g
Fits most any tool

]]></SDESC>
<DESC><![CDATA[An ice tool protector from Balck Diamond for gear transport.]]></DESC>
<NAME><![CDATA[Black Diamond Spike Protector]]></NAME>
<SRP>3.99</SRP>
<OUR_PRICE>3.99</OUR_PRICE>
<CLEAR>0.00</CLEAR>
<BMC>2.97</BMC>
<CONTRACT>2.50</CONTRACT>
<WEIGHT>12.5500</WEIGHT>
<QTY>3</QTY>
</Item>
<Item>
<ID>7</ID>
<CODE><![CDATA[PN9117]]></CODE>
<CATCODE>15000, 110041, 6002</CATCODE>
<SDESC><![CDATA[A tough shell helmet with foam top and closeable vents for all activities on rock.]]></SDESC>
<DESC><![CDATA[The Petzl Elios is well-proven as a durable, lightweight shell and foam helmet for all things rock-related. Comfortable and trustworthy, the two sizes between them cover the vast majority of heads, with full and easy adjustment for a secure fit every time.

This latest iteration of the classic comes with an extra too; sliding vent covers to reduce airflow in the cold or block out bits of gravel on a chossy route. Take it climbing, mountaineering, caving, canyoning, on via ferrata.... wherever you take it, you don't need to worry about it sitting in your pack for the walk-in as the ABS shell is tough enough to cope. Wherever there's a risk of your head meeting rock, the sturdy Elios adds solid protection without penalising you on weight.]]></DESC>
<NAME><![CDATA[Elios 2014]]></NAME>
<SRP>56.00</SRP>
<OUR_PRICE>56.00</OUR_PRICE>
<CLEAR>0.00</CLEAR>
<BMC>43.52</BMC>
<CONTRACT>43.52</CONTRACT>
<WEIGHT>25.2000</WEIGHT>
<QTY>6</QTY>
</Item>
<Item>
<ID>8</ID>
<CODE><![CDATA[PN9118]]></CODE>
<CATCODE>13000, 4007, 2010</CATCODE>
<SDESC><![CDATA[Smaller doesn't have to mean basic - a fully functional children's helmet rated for both climbing and cycling.]]></SDESC>
<DESC><![CDATA[With the Petzl Picchu on their head, your little one can be as adventurous as you like on the wall or on their bike. Maximising safety for precious heads, the Picchu is sized specifically for a comfortable fit on three to eight-year olds and even comes with stickers to personalise it to their taste.

The tough but lightweightABS shell is backed up inside with an expanded polystyrene liner for impact absorption, whilst comfort foam all round cushions contact points. It's small, but like most adult helmets it's furnished with headlamp loops and vents for full functionality, while the chin buckle is set off to the side for easy and comfortable fastening. So the Picchu genuinely is a regular climbing helmet sized for smaller heads - set your mind at greater ease and furnish your young adventurer with the protection they need in the Petzl Picchu helmet.]]></DESC>
<NAME><![CDATA[Picchu]]></NAME>
<SRP>41.00</SRP>
<OUR_PRICE>41.00</OUR_PRICE>
<CLEAR>0.00</CLEAR>
<BMC>35.00</BMC>
<CONTRACT>34.00</CONTRACT>
<WEIGHT>12.0000</WEIGHT>
<QTY>1</QTY>
</Item>
<Item>
<ID>9</ID>
<CODE><![CDATA[PN9134]]></CODE>
<CATCODE>110043, 11009, 120043</CATCODE>
<SDESC><![CDATA[The Jack-of-all-trades hat that's ready for a bit of rough and tumble whatever the weather.]]></SDESC>
<DESC><![CDATA[The Tilley TWC6 Outback Hat uses waxed cotton for water-resistant and durable headwear built for getting outdoors in all weathers. The hard-wearing material looks even better as it ages, attaining a leather-like look that works with the olive and tan design.

The medium brim on the TWC7 Outback Hat shields your face from the sun and rain from above, with a glare-reducing dark underbrim. Two Wind Cords (front and rear) hold it firmly on your head if the breeze gets up, while ventilation grommets ensure good airflow through the crown. This classic outdoor hat also has a layer of floating foam on top, a secret storage pocket and can be washed, packed and worn with the greatest ease. A style unto itself, the Outback Hat will serve you faithfully anywhere and everywhere you take it.

A Tilley Hat is guaranteed for life (yours, theirs, its) not to wear out - if you do manage to wear through yours, they'll send you a direct replacement at no charge. You also get a two-year 'insurance policy' against mishaps, whereby they will offer you a replacement hat at half the current retail price if your hat has an accident. A Tilley Hat is an investment for life, not just for this summer.]]></DESC>
<NAME><![CDATA[TWC7 Outback Medium Brim]]></NAME>
<SRP>67.00</SRP>
<OUR_PRICE>60.49</OUR_PRICE>
<CLEAR>0.00</CLEAR>
<BMC>54.44</BMC>
<CONTRACT>60.49</CONTRACT>
<WEIGHT>133.0000</WEIGHT>
<QTY>12</QTY>
</Item>
<Item>
<ID>10</ID>
<CODE><![CDATA[PN91003]]></CODE>
<CATCODE>1000, 8007, 8010</CATCODE>
<SDESC><![CDATA[The ultimate travel bag, made to be not only everlastingly rugged but totally travel-friendly too.]]></SDESC>
<DESC><![CDATA[The North Face Base Camp Duffel XL is a modern classic, the one you see standing up to all kinds of abuse in all kinds of situations all over the world. Swallowing a monster 155 litres of expedition kit, travel gear or sports equipment, the multitude of heroic handles, straps and attachment loops combined with about the toughest materials available makes carrying and securing the BCD in even the most unlikely places totally straightforward.

Tailored for travel, the double-zipped D-shaped flap is easy to load and sits open at base camp ready for you to find that vital small item when you need it. Plus of course there's a wide range of colours so you can virtually guarantee a uniquely recognisable sight on a luggage carousel. Trustworthy for whatever boundaries you're pushing, there's an excellent reason why smart travellers and the hardest of hardcore expeditionists choose The North Face Base Camp Duffel.]]></DESC>
<NAME><![CDATA[Base Camp Duffel Xlarge]]></NAME>
<SRP>120.00</SRP>
<OUR_PRICE>96.00</OUR_PRICE>
<CLEAR>0.00</CLEAR>
<BMC>86.40</BMC>
<CONTRACT>84.00</CONTRACT>
<WEIGHT>25.4500</WEIGHT>
<QTY>2</QTY>
</Item>
</Items>
</root>
